We are not stopping
until we find that smell.
Check out that black thing.
Was that even food?
I believe it was
cheese at one time.
No, that's not it.
-Ugh!
-Ew!
-Nope.
-No.
Hey, what about that?
Oh, God!
Isn't that the school rat
that Dewey was taking
care of last summer?
-No, that's not it.
-Keep looking.
♪ Yes, no, maybe ♪
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ Can you repeat
the question? ♪
♪ You're not the boss
of me now ♪
♪ You're not
the boss of me now ♪
♪ You're not the boss
of me now ♪
♪ And you're not so big ♪
♪ You're not the boss
of me now ♪
♪ You're not
the boss of me now ♪
♪ You're not the boss
of me now ♪
♪ And you're not so big ♪
♪ Life is unfair ♪
No, don't hang up.
We've almost made our decision.
I get three meat toppings
for the price of one!
No, no! Buy two pizzas,
get one free!
That's two free cheesepizzas!
I'd rather eat vomit!
The prospect of a deal
sends this family into a frenzy.
When you throw in pizza,
they need me to keep
from totally losing perspective.
Shut up, everyone!
Just shut up!
If we're not
having deep-dish,
then I swear I will tear up
these "free cheesy bread"
coupons right now!
Damn your cheesy bread!
I need toppings!
Why don't we just get
the stuffed crust special?
And lose my free bucket of soda?
Are you insane?!
Now, listen, Dennis,
I'm a reasonable man,
but I can't go back to my family
with a lot of lawyer talk
about coupon expiration dates.
So why don't we just reduce
the two three-fers to two-fers?
Five toppings on each,
and we'll just grandfather in
the wacky wings, okay?
No, no, hold on, hold on.
This call-waiting guy
will nottake a hint!
Hello. I can't talk right now.
I...
Yes.
What?
Dad, come on, you're
gonna lose those wings!
What?
My father died.
It was weird
going to Grandpa's funeral.
We hardly even knew
we had a grandpa,
and now we don't.
Reese is taking it really hard.
:
Why! Why!
Why couldn't he die
beforehe lost all his money?
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
It seems a little weird that
the second you come home
from your father's funeral,
you turn on Sports Bloopers.
-Hey.
-Hal...
it is not healthy to keep
all this bottled up.
I agree. I just don't have
anything to un-bottle.
I mean, I thought I'd cry
when I saw him in the box.
I thought I'd cry
when they closed it.
when they put it in the ground
and I threw dirt on him,
but... nothing.
Actually, I did get
a little misty
listening to the funeral
we passed on the way out.
Do you know that man
was the shoeshine guy
on the same corner for 40 years?
Hal, you don't have to be brave.
I'm not. You know me.
I cried at that movie
about the boxing wallaby.
I remember.
I think I'm not feeling anything
because I never really had
a relationship with him.
I mean, I suppose
he knew my name,
but he'd always just
called me "buddy."
Oh, Hal.
So, now a relationship that was
totally meaningless and trivial
is over.
It's hard to get too upset.
:
Hey, Lois. I'm returning
the Newsweekyou lent me
on Y2K.
It's okay, Abe.
Hal's asleep.
Good.
How's he doing?
Well, he seems to be doing fine,
but he can't be.
His father just died.
He got more upset when
his transmission gave out.
Well, he did just
have it rebuilt.
But I know what you're saying.
Sounds like he needs
to talk to someone.
Abe, thank you!
I know he respects you.
Not me.I don't want
to see him cry.
He needs to talk
to a professional.
A therapist?
No, a professional actor.
I suggest William Shatner,
TV's Captain Kirk.
What?
That's who I turn to
in a time of need.
Lois...
there's this wonderful service
where they hook up ordinary
people with celebrities.
You pay a fee,
and you get a phone
call from your choice
of participating
TV or movie stars.
Well, mostly TV stars.
And you think this is something
Hal would want?
Absolutely! He's a huge
fan of classic Trek.
It's not something you
share with your wife.
Lois, believe me,
I don't think I
would've gotten
through my social
anxiety disorder
without a few late-night
discussions with Agent Mulder.
It turns out the truth
was right in here.
Apparently, Shatner's
not available.
He's being knighted.
Well, thanks for trying, Abe.
Oh, it's not over yet.
I am not going to rest
until a classic TV star
puts Hal's spirit at ease.
:
I know you didn't love him,
but this is a funeral.
Don't you care?
You kidding?
About thisguy?
We weren't even close.
Check it out.
:
Now I'm happy.
Now I'm sad.
:
Oh, now I'm happy.
Boo-hoo, now I'm sad...
Hey, dead guy, why are
you hitting yourself?
Who knew we could have fun
with Dad?
That's who that is?
I thought it was, like,
a math teacher or something.
Why aren't you sad?
Why aren't you throwing
yourselves on my coffin
and begging to be buried
instead of me?
Are you guys feeling
as little as I am?
I felt sadder
when my wart fell off.
I guess he just didn't make
much of an impression on us
when he was alive.
HAL:
Boys...
boys, don't go.
Oh...
Dewey,
you always loved me.
No, boys!
Don't you miss me?
Imiss me.
Wake up, boys! You don't want
breakfast to melt!
-Ice cream?
-Well, last time I checked,
you can't have a sundae bar
without it.
HAL :
Wake up, Malcolm.
Aah!
Dad... it's 5:00 in the morning.
Well, I couldn't sleep
until my sons are as happy
as I can make them.
Today's special,
every scoop comes
with a hug!
And it doesn't stop here.
We've got a full day
of pick-up basketball
in the park,
a barbecue, more ice cream,
then I thought we'd take a nap
underneath a tree,
and then catch fireflies.
What about school?
I've got that covered.
Please excuse my son.
He has... the flu...
explosive diarrhea...
a rare bone disease...
We may have to get you a cane.
-Cool!
-Does Mom know?
Please, will you let me worry
about your mom, okay?
Seriously, though,
don't tell her.
Now, who wants a ride
on top of the car?
Abe, I appreciate what you're
trying to do, but I'm not...
Lois, do you know
what it cost me to get
Leonard Nimoy's private number?
Ferengi noses
don't grow on trees.
-Let's just...
-It's ringing!
: Hello?
Mr. Nimoy?
This is he.
We apologize for disturbing
an important man like yourself.
But my friend's father
just died,
and he could use some sage
advice from a learned actor-
director-poet-
photographer-vocalist.
Uh, I'm sorry,
but in Star Trek II:
The Wrath of Khan,
was Ricardo Montalban
the gentlemen he seems to be?
Because a little birdy
told me...
-Abe!
-NIMOY: I'd be happy
to help your friend.
It's very sad
when a man loses his father.
I've been through loss myself.
Oh, that's very kind
of you, Mr. Nimoy.
I'm his wife.
So will this be charged
to your credit card?
What?
Well, that's eight dollars
a minute for the Nimoy.
And for another five,
I'll leave an outgoing message on your answering machine as...
:
Mr. Bob Hope!
How about that Brooke Shields?
She's got legs that go all
the way down to the ground...
Wow!
Nimoy's Bob Hope is great.
Is there nothing
the man can't do?
Hey.
You doing okay?
Oh, yeah, you know, I'll drop
the kids off at school,
maybe look through
a photo album.
Well, that's what
bereavement days are for.
I love you.
I love you, too.
:
Okay!
Yeah!
Clear shot to the refrigerator.
Who's gonna stop me?
Whoo!
Yeah!
Nice!
Mmm.
Pudding!
:
It's your mother!
MALCOLM: Hurry!
Oh, hi, honey.
God, I hate school.
What's to eat
in this dump?
-Good night, boys.
-Good night, Dad.
What a day.
Memorable, huh?
And if you thought
today was fun,
tomorrow's gonna make it
look like garbage.
Quick question.
If I died in my sleep tonight,
who'd be sad?
I would!
Me! Me!
Sure. Of course
we'd be sad.
You boys have just earned
some s'mores.
Back in a jiff.
Wait, Dad.
You don't have
to do this.
I think I know
what's going on.
If you want to
talk about stuff...
Malcolm, all I'm interested in
right now
is filling your bellies
with marshmallow-y goodness.
-But, Dad...
-Don't worry.
I'll make yours double thick.
This is so awesome.
Yeah. I don't know what alien
worm burrowed into Dad's brain,
but I'd like to shake its hand.
Don't you guys see
what's going on?
This is all because of Grandpa.
Ever since he died,
Dad's been feeling bad
because he doesn't
miss him enough.
So now he's trying to compensate
by bonding with us.
That's just a lot
of fancy language
for all-you-can-eat s'mores.
This isn't fun and games, Reese.
He's got a real
emotional problem.
You think Dad could really be
doing this to buy our love?
I guess.
I say we squeeze him
for all he's got.
It's the least we
could do for him.
Where's Dad?
It was weird.
I got up early
this morning
and found him sitting
at the kitchen table
looking at a picture
of him and Grandpa
with this peaceful
smile on his face.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Then he said he
really worked
some things out
last night.
And then he just
took off for work.
Wow.
Hey, get your greedy
mitts off my lunch!
I was just moving it
to get to my lunch.
What lunch?
Later.
Get off me!
Found you!
Hey!
Well, you have to admit
it was pretty good
hiding place.
-I was in there for over
an hour!
-I helped.
And you should
share the prize.
Hey, where's Malcolm?
He had to go to school.
Yeah, he said this was stupid.
Too bad. I guess
he misses out on Motocross!
Sweet!
I mean, I guess it's okay.
Come on. It'll be
better than yesterday.
What was yesterday?
I can't quite remember.
Can you, Dewey?
I knocked you
into pudding.
I guess the problem with
memories is they fade.
Especially in the minds
of young people
that are scrambled with
video games and death metal.
I can barely remember
my own name.
Hey, you know
what doesn't fade?
Things.
Like these pants.
I can still remember
the crisp September day
when Mom gave them to us.
She had a little lipstick
on her upper tooth.
Her eyes crinkled...
She smelled like lilacs.
Hey, you know what?
Ican get you things.
I don't know.
You'd have to drive us to
some kind of mall or something.
You boys go get in the car.
I'm going to call
the credit card company
and have them up my limit.
Taken care of.
Nice.
It's just a shame I'll have
to catch it with a dirty mitt.
I want to remember
how great you are in spring,
summer, fall...
and winter, too.
Wow, Dad, you bought
the whole store!
Nobody's got
a better dad than us.
Except Joe Garoogian.
Dewey!
You don't deserve
to remember
how good Dad is.
You only deserve to remember me
whacking the crap out of you.
Not so fast, Reese.
The boy's just being honest.
Now tell me,
what is it about this Joe's
father that's so great?
His dad's vice president
of an electronics company.
He can get any type of TV,
video game or stereo he wants.
Is there an electronics store
near here?
Tech Boys on Willow.
Price Town's closer,
but they have crap
for high-def.
I've got something for Hal
that I think may
do the trick.
Abe, I thought
we were done with this.
I thought we were, too, Lois,
until 3:00 this morning
when I found myself in a
collectibles auction site
and saw this baby.
Yes, it's a Vulcan lyre
with ten preprogrammed
Christmas carols.
Abe, I'm sorry.
I know you're trying to help,
but this is not what Hal needs.
You're right.
I guess I got carried
away and lost sight
of what got us started
in the first place...
to hook Hal up with a member of
the original cast of Star Trek.
That's not what got
this started.
Abe, Hal's father died.
And I will not let him
die in vain.
I will call Sulu.
I will call Chekhov.
And if they say no,
so help me,
I will call the Gorn.
Abe, stop, just stop.
I appreciate
you trying to help,
but I don't need
any of this.
I'm going to take Hal
to a bed and breakfast
for a nice weekend,
and that's it.
He just needs
some emotional comfort.
So you think a weekend
of nurturing and sex
is going to get him
through this?
Do you even know this man?!
What the hell's all this?
Turns out Dad still has
some grieving left to do.
I can't believe you.
You lied to me
and you totally
took advantage of him.
I don't see it that way.
They say money
can't buy love...
but they're wrong.
I'm actually
starting to love Dad.
Now I'm not saying
somebody couldn't come
along and outbid him,
but right now,
he's the front-runner.
You can't do this.
This is wrong.
You're giving all this back.
Who are you
to question his process?
Reese, he's crazy.
Mom's crazy.
But she's the kind of crazy
where all she does
is yell at us and punish.
Now Dad's crazy in a way
where he buys us an Xbox 360.
And you want to mess with that?
You're just afraid
of happiness, Malcolm.
You can delude yourself
all you want.
All this is going back
to the store.
Hey, give that back!
You had your chance!
Reese, this is over!
This is the only good thing
that's ever happened around here
and you're ruining it!
Boys! What are you doing?
Today's a happy day.
You're supposed to remember
this the rest of your lives.
I need to talk to you, Dad.
Dad, if you love us,
don't listen to him.
Look at what you're doing.
Look at the money
you're spending.
Look at the reason
why you're spending it.
Something is very wrong.
I hear you, Malcolm.
I understand that things have
gotten a little unbalanced
and I know what
I need to do.
Thank God.
I'm going to buy you a car.
It's moments like this
that really define character.
I love you, Daddy!
No, it's not our honeymoon,
but I would like
the honeymoon suite.
What?
No, that must be a mistake.
My credit card
can't be maxed out.
I just paid the bill.
Reese!
Get me out of this.
Malcolm's getting a car.
We only did this
so Dad wouldn't buy us
something more expensive.
I miss Grandpa.
I know this is wrong.
But somehow my body's not doing
anything to stop it.
Maybe that means at some level,
I don't even know it's wrong.
And if I don't know
if it's wrong,
then I can't get blamed
for doing it.
Right?
Now, the high-tech package
comes with a CG
rearview imaging system,
a GPS and a DVD.
I don't absolutely need
a DVD player.
Sure you do, Malcolm.
Every time you stop
at a red light,
I want you watching movies,
thinking of your dad.
-What else have we got?
-Want the sports package?
That's like asking
if we want doors.
There it is,
every option we offer,
including some
I didn't even know about.
Floor mats have
undercoating.
Comes with
a 14-year warranty.
We don't sell
many of those.
All it needs...
is your signature.
Huh...
What?
My dad had this same pen.
He must've been a great guy.
This is a great pen.
We don't really need
to get into that right now.
See, I just lost my dad.
I'm sorry.
Bet he would've loved
to have seen his grandson
driving that sports pack.
You know...
I don't know
if he would have.
He was pretty
emotionally distant.
He had a lot of trouble
showing love.
Yeah.
Old-timers, eh?
But I didn't care.
I didn't care
if he had trouble.
I loved him.
He was my dad.
You know, I see that
you're in a lot of pain
right now...
I'm going to need some
grief counseling, too,
if I let you take me up on
this offer I'm giving you.
I remember coming downstairs
in the morning
and he would be at the table
and he would say, "Hey, buddy,
"I'm doing four things at once:
"I'm watching TV,
I'm reading the newspaper,
I'm drinking coffee,
and I'm talking to you."
Isn't that amazing?
You know, I got a guy
whose wife died
who's looking at
this car, so...
He didn't have to do
anything for me.
He was my dad.
Dad...
you don't have to do
anything for me, either.
But if you want to...
that'd be great.
I lost my dad.
I know.
Hello?
I'm George Takei.
I played Sulu on Star Trek.
Did your grandfather
die recently?
Yes.
Allow me to extend
my deepest condolences.
I got a call
from a neighbor
that your father might
like to talk to me.
And when I called back,
the line was busy.
So I decided to come over.
It was a six-hour bus ride
with a lot of stops.
May I have some water, please?
Sorry, my parents aren't home.
But you can use
the hose out front.
Delightful.
If you don't mind,
I'll make camp
on your front lawn
in anticipation
of their return.
Improvisation:
my stock and trade.
In episode 18,
"The Squire of Gothos,"
the script read,
"the crew ad-libs 'hello.'"
Well, I was off
to the races.
Well, I've got
a lot of homework.
Ooh, mushrooms!
May I help myself?
Captioned by Post Haste Digital